oreillyauto.com 2006-03-11

# O'Reilly Auto Parts

| 

Your Privacy is Important to Us 

At O'Reilly Auto Parts maintaining your privacy is a top priority. Our website was designed with your privacy in mind and any information supplied will be used for the sole purpose of improving our relationship with our customers. 

The following policy overviews our commitment to protecting our customers' privacy and is broken down into the following areas: Personal Information, Customer Rights, and Security. 

|   
---  
|  Personal Information   
---  
  
  * _What is collected_  
On some O'Reilly web pages, you can order products or services, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are name, contact and billing information, transaction, and credit card information.
  * In order to tailor our website to continuously improve our products and services, we may also ask you to voluntarily provide us with information regarding your personal or professional interests, demographics, experience with our products, and contact preferences.
  * _How is it used_  
O'Reilly uses your information to better understand your needs and provide you with better service. Specifically, we use your information to help you complete a transaction, to communicate back to you, to update you on service and benefits, and to personalize our web sites for you. Credit card numbers are used only for payment processing and are not retained for other purposes. Data collected online may also be combined with information you provide when you register your ownership of O'Reilly products. 
  * _Who we share it with_  
O'Reilly will not sell, rent, or lease your personal information to any others. Unless we have your direct permission or are required by law, we will only share the personal data you provide online with other O'Reilly entities and/or business partners who are acting on our behalf for the uses described above. Such O'Reilly entities and/or business partners, including those in the United States and/or any other countries, are governed by our privacy policies with respect to the use of this data and are bound by the appropriate confidentiality agreements.

|  Customer's Rights   
---  
O'Reilly will not use or share any of the personal information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without first letting you know and offering you a choice. As previously stated, we will also provide you the opportunity to let us know if you do not wish to receive unsolicited direct marketing materials from us and we will do everything we can to honor such requests. Local country laws and policies are applied where they differ from those in the U.S.   
|  Security   
---  
O'Reilly is committed to ensuring the security of your information. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.   
|  Questions or Comments   
---  
If you have comments or questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us using our **e-mail link below** , or by calling (417) 874-7161.
